chromeindustries.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy Policy | Chrome Industries

At Chrome ("CHROME," "we," or "us"), we are committed to the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how personal information is collected from users of the CHROME website at [www.chromeindustries.com](http://www.chromeindustries.com/) (the "Site"), and how that information is used and disclosed. By using our Site, you consent to the terms of this Policy.

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time and will notify you of such changes by posting the modified Policy on our Site and indicating at the top of the Policy the date it was last updated. If there are material changes to this Policy, we will notify you more directly.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

You provide personal information to us in a number of ways when you visit the Site. For example, you provide us with personal information when you:

  * • Create or update an account or profile and subscribe to our e-mail newsletter or other services ("Services");
  * • Purchase CHROME products on the Site;
  * • Participate in a survey, contest, sweepstakes, or other promotions on the Site;
  * • Contact us by e-mail for any reason, such as to request help with the Services, or to provide us with your comments/feedback;
  * • Submit personal information in connection with photos/stories for our potential use and/or publication.

We may collect your name, image, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date. We may also collect certain demographic information in connection with your participation in any survey, contest, sweepstakes, or promotion on the Site such as gender, birth day and month, city, state and country, websites and personal interests.

Additionally, when you visit our Site, some information is automatically collected, such as your computer's operating system and browser type, version, and capabilities (such as whether JavaScript is enabled and cookies are accepted), your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time and date of your visit, the referring site (if applicable), as well as screen resolution, color and depth. This information is tracked through the use of web beacons, cookies and logs.

Cookies. We may automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer by your browser at the request of a Web site to store your personal preferences. Among other things, the use of cookies helps us to improve the Site and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing the Site, to personalize your experience, and to remember your preferences. If your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access certain features or services of the Site. For a full list of cookies used on ChromeIndustries.com, view our [Cookies Page](http://www.chromeindustries.com/cookies).

Web Beacons. "Web beacons" (also known as "web bugs," "action tags," "pixel trackers," or "clear GIFs") may also be used on the Site or in our emails. Web beacons are small graphic images placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an e-mail message that allow the collection of certain information and monitor user activity on the Site or in emails. Web beacons are invisible because of their size (only 1 by 1 pixel) and because they are the same color as the background of the web page. Web beacons are used to collect the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the Web user comes from and the time the Web beacon is activated (such as when you view the webpage, advertisement, or e-mail that contains the Web beacon).

## HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION

In general, we use personal information collected on the Site to provide the Services and otherwise process transactions on the Site, to provide support for the Services, to respond to user requests and inquiries, to maintain a record of our dealings with Site users, to develop and improve products and services, to inform users about products or services we think will be of interest and to allow users to connect or search for other customers that share similar interests.

When we use your personal information in our marketing efforts, we provide you with choices (see "Choice," below). We may also receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, and may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you (for example, we may receive updated information about you, such as an updated billing address, from the financial institution issuing your credit card in connection with billing for CHROME products).

## SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION

We do not share, sell, trade, or rent personal information to third parties, including for their own marketing purposes without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy. We may share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in operating our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing traffic information or other data, providing marketing assistance to us, mailing items, processing credit card transactions, and fulfilling or delivering orders. In all cases, we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions.

We also disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a subpoena, warrant or court order) or respond to lawful requests and legal process; to enforce or apply this Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect the rights and property of Chrome, our agents, our community members, our customers' and others; to protect our community members, customers and others from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of the Site or Services; or if we reasonably believe that disclosure is needed to respond to an emergency or protect the personal safety of any person.

In addition, information about our customers, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed or transferred as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets.

## CHILDREN

We encourage parents to take an active interest in their children's use of the Internet. The Site is not designed to collect personal information from children who are under 13 years of age, and we do not intend to or knowingly collect such information. If you are under 13, you should not provide personal information on our Site.

## SECURITY

We use reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, destruction and alteration of information while it is under our control. We cannot, however, guarantee the protection of information against such events, nor can we promise that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.

When you register for an account on the Site, we ask you to create a password. To protect the confidentiality of your personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused or otherwise misappropriated.

## CHOICE

To opt-out of receiving marketing or other promotional communications from us, to access, change or delete your personal information maintained by us, or to otherwise change your choices about how we use your personal information we provide you with the following options: you may (1) follow the "Unsubscribe" instructions contained in the communication from us; (2) e-mail us at [support@chromeindustries.com](mailto:support@chromeindustries.com) or (3) write to us at the following address with your request:

Chrome Attn: Online Customer Service 580 4th Street, San Francisco, CA 94107

Opt-out requests will not apply to transactional service messages, including security alerts and notices about your current account and services.

## YOUR COMMENTS

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this Policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach us via e-mail at [support@chromeindustries.com](mailto:support@chromeindustries.com)

Date of Last Revision: February 20, 2013

### PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND ALL TERMS, POLICIES AND GUIDELINES INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE.

These terms and conditions of use (“Site Terms”) apply exclusively to your access to, and use of, Chrome's ("CHROME”) website at www.chromebagsstore.com (the "Site"). These Site Terms do not alter in any way the terms or conditions of any other agreement you may have with CHROME, or its subsidiaries or affiliates, for products, services or otherwise. If you are using the Site on behalf of any entity, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to accept these Site Terms on such entity's behalf, and that such entity agrees to indemnify you and CHROME for violations of these Site Terms.

CHROME reserves the right to change or modify these Site Terms and/or any policy or guideline of the Site at any time in its sole discretion. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting of the revisions on the Site, and you waive any right you may have to receive specific notice of such changes or modifications. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes or modifications will confirm your acceptance of such changes or modifications. Therefore, you should frequently review the Site Terms and applicable policies on the Site to understand the terms and conditions that apply to your use of the Site. If you do not agree to the amended terms, you must stop using the Site.

If you have any questions about the use of the Site, please send them to [support@chromeindustries.com](mailto:support@chromeindustries.com) or the mailing address listed below.

Chrome Industries, Inc.  
580 4th Street  
San Francisco, CA 94107

### 1\. Privacy Policy

Please refer to our Privacy Policy for information on how CHROME collects, uses and discloses personally identifiable information from its users.

### 2\. Copyright and Limited License

Unless otherwise indicated, the Site and all content and other materials on the Site, including, without limitation, the CHROME logo, and all designs, text, graphics, pictures, information, data, software, sound files, other files and the selection and arrangement thereof (collectively, the "Site Materials") are the proprietary property of CHROME or its licensors or users and are protected by U.S. and international copyright and/or other intellectual property laws.

You are granted a limited, non-sublicensable license to access and use the Site and electronically copy (except where prohibited without a license) and print to hard copy portions of the Site Materials solely for your informational, non-commercial and personal use, or to purchase CHROME products. Such license is subject to these Site Terms and does not include: (a) any resale or commercial use of the Site or the Site Materials therein; (b) the collection and use of any product listings, pictures or descriptions; (c) the distribution, public performance or public display of any Site Materials, (d) modifying or otherwise making any derivative uses of the Site and the Site Materials, or any portion thereof; (e) use of any data mining, robots or similar data gathering or extraction methods; (f) downloading (other than page caching) of any portion of the Site, the Site Materials or any information contained therein, except as expressly permitted on the Site; or (g) any use of the Site or the Site Materials other than for its intended purpose. Any use of the Site or the Site Materials other than as specifically authorized herein, without the prior written permission of CHROME, is strictly prohibited and will terminate the license granted herein. Such unauthorized use may also violate applicable laws including without limitation copyright and trademark laws and applicable communications regulations and statutes. Unless explicitly stated herein, nothing in these Site Terms shall be construed as conferring any license to intellectual property rights, whether by estoppel, implication or otherwise. This license is revocable at any time.

### 3\. Repeat Infringer Policy

In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) and other applicable law, CHROME has adopted a policy of terminating, in appropriate circumstances and at CHROME's sole discretion, subscribers or account holders who are deemed to be repeat infringers. CHROME may also at its sole discretion limit access to the Site and/or terminate the accounts of any users who infringe any intellectual property rights of others, whether or not there is any repeat infringement.

### 6\. Hyperlinks

You are granted a limited, non-exclusive right to create a text hyperlink to the Site for noncommercial purposes, provided such link does not portray CHROME or any of its products and services in a false, misleading, derogatory or otherwise defamatory manner and provided further that the linking site does not contain any adult or illegal material or any material that is offensive, harassing or otherwise objectionable. This limited right may be revoked at any time. You may not use a CHROME logo or other proprietary graphic of CHROME to link to this Site without the express written permission of CHROME. Further, you may not use, frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any CHROME trademark, logo or other proprietary information, including the images found at the Site, the content of any text or the layout/design of any page or form contained on a page on the Site without CHROME's express written consent. Except as noted above, you are not conveyed any right or license by implication, estoppel or otherwise in or under any patent, trademark, copyright or proprietary right of CHROME or any third party.

CHROME makes no claim or representation regarding, and accepts no responsibility for, the quality, content, nature or reliability of third-party websites accessible by hyperlink from the Site, or websites linking to the Site. Such sites are not under the control of CHROME, and CHROME is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site, or any review, changes or updates to such sites. CHROME provides links from the Site to third-party websites only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply affiliation, endorsement or adoption by CHROME of any site or any information contained therein. When you leave the Site, you should be aware that our terms and policies no longer govern. Please review the applicable terms and policies (including, for example, the privacy policy) of any third-party website that you link to from the Site before you use such third-party site.

### 7\. Third Party Content

The Site may provide access to third party content and/or links to third-party websites (collectively the "Third-Party Content") as a service to those interested in this information. CHROME does not have any control over, and does not endorse or adopt, any Third Party Content and can make no guarantee as to its accuracy or completeness. CHROME does not represent or warrant the accuracy of any information contained therein and undertakes no responsibility to update or review any Third Party Content. Users access and use such Third Party Content at their own risk.

### 8\. Advertisements and Promotions; Third-Party Products and Services

CHROME may run advertisements and promotions from third parties on the Site or may otherwise provide information about or links to third-party products or services on the Site. Your business dealings or correspondence with, or participation in promotions of, such third parties, and any terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings or promotions, are solely between you and such third party. CHROME is not responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings or promotions or as the result of the presence of such non-CHROME advertisers or third-party information on the Site.

By participating in CHROME promotions, including without limitation CHROME sweepstakes and contests, you agree that CHROME may use your information for marketing and promotional purposes.

### 11\. Registration Data; Account Security

In consideration of your use of the Site, you agree to (a) provide accurate, current and complete information about you as may be prompted by any registration forms on the Site ("Registration Data"); (b) maintain the security of your password and identification; (c) maintain and promptly update the Registration Data, and any other information you provide to CHROME, to keep it accurate, current and complete; and (d) accept all risks of unauthorized access to the Registration Data and any other information you provide to CHROME.

### 12\. Indemnification

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless CHROME, its parent companies, subsidiaries, and affiliates and each of their respective independent contractors, service providers, consultants, directors, members, employees, agents, agencies, and professional advisors (individually and together, the "CHROME Parties"), from and against any claims, damages, costs, liabilities and expenses (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys' fees) arising out of or related to any content you post, store or otherwise transmit on or through the Site (including, without limitation, and User Content and Submissions) or your use of or inability to use the Site (including, without limitation, the Interactive Areas), including without limitation any actual or threatened suit, demand or claim made against the CHROME Parties, arising out of or relating to the User Content, your conduct, your violation of these Site Terms or any other CHROME terms, policies or agreements available on or through the Site, or your violation of the rights of any third party.

### 13\. Disclaimer

EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED TO THE CONTRARY IN WRITING BY CHROME, THE SITE, THE SITE MATERIALS CONTAINED THEREIN AND THE SERVICES PROVIDED ON OR IN CONNECTION THEREWITH (THE "SERVICES") ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. CHROME DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT AS TO THE INFORMATION, CONTENT AND MATERIALS IN THE SITE. CHROME DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE SITE MATERIALS OR THE SERVICES ARE ACCURATE, COMPLETE, RELIABLE, CURRENT OR ERROR-FREE. CHROME DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE SITE OR ITS SERVERS ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. CHROME IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONDUCT, WHETHER ONLINE OR OFFLINE, OF ANY USER OF THE SITE OR THE SERVICE, AND YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER USERS. PRODUCT REVIEWS AND COMMENTS ARE STRICTLY THE OPINION OF THE USER POSTING SUCH REVIEWS OR COMMENTS, AND CHROME DOES NOT ENDORSE OR APPROVE AND SUCH REVIEWS OR COMMENTS.

CHROME IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS OR OMISSIONS RELATING TO PRICING, TEXT OR PHOTOGRAPHY. WHILE CHROME ATTEMPTS TO MAKE YOUR ACCESS AND USE OF THE SITE AND THE SERVICES SAFE, CHROME CANNOT AND DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE SITE OR ITS SERVER(S) ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS; THEREFORE, YOU SHOULD USE INDUSTRY-RECOGNIZED SOFTWARE TO DETECT AND DISINFECT VIRUSES FROM ANY DOWNLOAD.

CHROME reserves the right to change any and all content contained in the Site and any Services offered through the Site at any time without notice. Reference to any third-party products, services, processes or other information, by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, supplier or otherwise does not constitute or imply endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation thereof, or any affiliation therewith, by CHROME.

### 14\. Limitation of Liability

IN NO EVENT SHALL CHROME OR ANY CHROME PARTIES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF PROFITS OR LOSS OF DATA, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO NEGLIGENCE) OR OTHERWISE, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, THE SERVICES, THE SITE MATERIALS OR OTHER MATERIALS OR INFORMATION CONTAINED IN OR ACCESSED THROUGH THE SITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY DAMAGES CAUSED BY OR RESULTING FROM RELIANCE BY USER ON ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM CHROME, OR THAT RESULT FROM MISTAKES, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DELETION OF FILES OR E-MAIL, ERRORS, DEFECTS, VIRUSES, DELAYS IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION OR ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, WHETHER OR NOT RESULTING FROM ACTS OF GOD, COMMUNICATIONS FAILURE, THEFT, DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO CHROME'S RECORDS, PROGRAMS OR SERVICES. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF CHROME, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, WARRANTY, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE, WHETHER ACTIVE, PASSIVE OR IMPUTED), PRODUCT LIABILITY, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHER THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE EXCEED ANY COMPENSATION YOU PAY, IF ANY, TO CHROME FOR ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE SITE.

### 15\. Applicable Law and Venue

These Site Terms and your use of the Site shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, applicable to agreements made and to be entirely performed within the State of California, without resort to its conflict of law provisions.

### 16\. Termination

Notwithstanding any of these Site Terms, CHROME reserves the right, without notice and in its sole discretion, to terminate your license to use the Site, and to block or prevent your future access to and use of the Site.

### 17\. Severability

If any provision of these Site Terms shall be deemed unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from these Site Terms and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.

### 18\. Questions & Contact Information

Questions or comments about the Site may be directed to CHROME at following postal and email addresses:

CHROME Inc.   
ATTN: Online Customer Service  
580 4th Street  
San Francisco, CA 94107   
Email:[ support@chromeindustries.com](mailto:support@chromeindustries.com)
